A Guide to the Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files, 1964-1965
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- General Files, 1964-1965
  - Office - Travel 1964-1965 (Box 32)
  - "P - Ph" Miscellaneous 1964-1965 (Box 33)
  - "Pi - Pz" Miscellaneous 1964-1965 (Box 33)
  - Page-Barbour Lectures (see page-Barbour Committee) (folder empty) 1964-1965 (Box 33)
  - Personnel (Richmond and Local Offices) 1964-1965 (Box 33)
  - Phi Beta Kappa 1964-1965 (Box 33)
  - Philosophy (folder empty) 1964-1965 (Box 33)
  - Photographs (folder empty) 1964-1965 (Box 33)
  - Physics 1964-1965 (Box 33)
  - Planning Department (see also individual building programs) 1964-1965 (Box 33)
  - President's Council 1964-1965 (Box 33)
  - Psychology (folder empty) 1964-1965 (Box 33)
  - Public Relations 1964-1965 (Box 35)
  - Publications 1964-1965 (Box 35)
  - Purchasing (Richmond and University) 1964-1965 (Box 35)
  - "Q" Miscellaneous 1964-1965 (Box 35)
  - Questionnaires and Inquiries 1964-1965 (Box 35)
  - "R" Miscellaneous 1964-1965 (Box 35)
  - Radiation Protection (folder empty) 1964-1965 (Box 35)
  - Radio (folder empty) 1964-1965 (Box 35)
  - Raven Society 1964-1965 (Box 35)
  - Recommendations 1964-1965 (Box 35)
  - Registrar 1964-1965 (Box 35)
  - Registrar - Reports 1964-1965 (Box 35)
  - Rehabilitation Center 1964-1965 (Box 35)
  - Seven Society 1964-1965 (Box 36)
  - Shannon - Space Executive Tour 1964-1965 (Box 36)
  - Sociology and Anthropology (folder empty) 1964-1965 (Box 36)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools (see also Institutional Self-Study) 1964-1965 (Box 36)
  - Southern Fellowships Fund (see also Council of Southern Universities) 1964-1965 (Box 36)
  - Southern Regional Education Board 1964-1965 (Box 36)
  - Southern University Conference 1964-1965 (Box 37)
  - Space Utilization 1964-1965 (Box 37)
  - Speech - Alumni (folder empty) 1964-1965 (Box 37)
  - Speech - Finals: George Mason College, 9 June 1965 1964-1965 (Box 37)
  - Speech - Law Day, 8 May 1965 (folder empty) 1964-1965 (Box 37)
  - Speech - The Necessity of the Humanities, 21 March 1965 1964-1965 (Box 37)
  - Speech - Charlottesville-Albemarle Real Estate Board, 10 December 1964 (folder empty) 1964-1965 (Box 37)
  - Speech - Universities, Colleges, and Local Government, 31 August 1964 1964-1965 (Box 37)
  - Speech - Summer School Finals, 15 August 1964 1964-1965 (Box 37)
  - Speeches 1964-1965 (Box 37)
  - Speech and Drama 1964-1965 (Box 37)
  - State Council of Higher Education 1964-1965 (Box 37)
  - State Department of Education 1964-1965 (Box 37)
  - State Universities Association (see also Association of American Universities for joint business) 1964-1965 (Box 37)
  - Statistics 1964-1965 (Box 37)
  - Student Aid and Placement (see also Fellowships and Scholarships) 1964-1965 (Box 37)
  - Student Aid Committee on Student Financial Aid 1964-1965 (Box 38)
  - Student Affairs 1964-1965 (Box 38)
  - Student Council 1964-1965 (Box 38)
  - Student Health Department 1964-1965 (Box 38)
  - Summer Session 1964-1965 (Box 38)
  - Summer Session - Finals 1964-1965 (Box 38)
  - "T" Miscellaneous 1964-1965 (Box 38)
  - Tax Study Commission 1964-1965 (Box 38)
  - Traffic Control 1964-1965 (Box 38)
  - "U" Miscellaneous 1964-1965 (Box 38)
  - U. S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare 1964-1965 (Box 39)
  - U. S. Department of State 1964-1965 (Box 39)
  - U. S. Naval Academy 1964-1965 (Box 39)
  - University Center in Virginia 1964-1965 (Box 39)
  - University Hall (see also Field House Committee) 1964-1965 (Box 39)
  - University Houses 1964-1965 (Box 39)
  - University Houses - Faulkner House 1964-1965 (Box 39)
  - University Houses - "Morea" 1964-1965 (Box 39)
  - University Press of Virginia 1964-1965 (Box 40)
  - University Printing Office 1964-1965 (Box 40)
  - "V" Miscellaneous 1964-1965 (Box 40)
  - Virginia Academy of Science 1964-1965 (Box 40)
  - Virginia Associated Research Council (see special files) 1964-1965 (Box 40)
  - Virginia College Building Authority 1964-1965 (Box 40)
  - Virginia Commission on Higher Educational Facilities 1964-1965 (Box 40)
  - Virginia Education Association 1964-1965 (Box 40)
  - Virginia Foundation for Independent Colleges 1964-1965 (Box 40)
  - Virginia Historical Society (see also Madison Papers) 1964-1965 (Box 40)
  - Virginia Legislative Advisory Council (see Legislative Program and Budget) 1964-1965 (Box 40)
  - Virginia Quarterly Review 1964-1965 (Box 40)
  - Virginia State Chamber of Commerce 1964-1965 (Box 40)
  - Virginia Student Aid Foundation 1964-1965 (Box 40)
  - Visitors - Called Meeting 1964-1965 (Box 41)
  - Visitors - Committees 1964-1965 (Box 41)
  - Visitors - General 1964-1965 (Box 41)
  - Visitors - Docket, 16 October 1964 1964-1965 (Box 42)
  - Visitors - Minutes, 16 October 1964 1964-1965 (Box 42)
  - Visitors - Docket, 12 December 1964 1964-1965 (Box 42)
  - Visitors - Minutes, 12 December 1964 1964-1965 (Box 42)
  - Visitors - Docket, 9 April 1965 1964-1965 (Box 42)
  - Visitors - Minutes, 9 April 1965 1964-1965 (Box 43)
  - Visitors - Docket, 4 June 1965 1964-1965 (Box 43)
  - Visitors - Minutes, 4 June 1965 1964-1965 (Box 43)
  - Visitors - Docket, 6 February 1965 1964-1965 (Box 43)
  - Visitors - Minutes, 6 February 1965 1964-1965 (Box 43)
  - Visitors - Frank Talbott, Jr. (Visitor retired; see file under 'T') 1964-1965 (Box 43)
  - "W - Wh" Miscellaneous 1964-1965 (Box 44)
  - "Wi - Wz" Miscellaneous 1964-1965 (Box 44)
  - Walpole Society 1964-1965 (Box 44)
  - Washington Center for Metropolitan Studies 1964-1965 (Box 44)
  - Water Resources 1964-1965 (Box 44)
  - Women, Dean of 1964-1965 (Box 44)
  - "X - Y - Z" Miscellaneous 1964-1965 (Box 44)
  - YMCA 1964-1965 (Box 44)
  - "N" Miscellaneous 1964-1965 (Box 45)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (see also VARC) 1964-1965 (Box 45)
  - National Association of State Universities (folder empty) 1964-1965 (Box 45)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges - General 1964-1965 (Box 45)